<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Digital Cloud]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>site-lib/media/favicon.svg</url><title>Digital Cloud</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 02:31:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="site-lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 02:31:58 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[Home]]></title><description><![CDATA[Welcome to my Digital Cloud! This is a work in progress for now, but thanks for visiting! Soon it'll have much more to explore.For now, go back to my main website at -&gt; <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://kareem.cloud" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://kareem.cloud" target="_self">kareem.cloud</a>]]></description><link>home.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Home.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 02:31:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Note Taking Fails]]></title><description><![CDATA[We create and consume notes in different ways. Why do we take notes? This will be different for everyone but a few common reasons are: recall, discovery of new ideas, connections, helping you think about content you consume, and creating content.
NotesYouCreate- Unstructured- Chaotic- Disconnected- RapidYouConsume- Grouped- Tagged- Structured- Well paced- SearchableNotes
Fundamentally you will always have an easier time creating notes one way and consuming them another way. This isn't new information this is why note taking systems and tools emerge. Obsidian is a famous tool for this as it simplifies connecting disparate ideas in the hopes of emerging content, connections, and recallThe problem is obsidian doesn't do that for you, it can't. It provides tools to enable this like connections, tagging, filters, grouping, embedding and so on. Ideally once done, it should be quite easy to go back through your notes.
RawNotesYouProcessedNotesTagGroupFilterFilter1-4x the effort of the original note takingConsume
However, these systems can take as long as or longer than creating the original notes. They also require attentiveness and discipline in a single framework. In my experience the way you think or like to read changes not only over time but from subject to subject making this inherently unsustainable unless you dedicate massive amounts of time to organization alone.Due to this many note taking solutions fail.
<a data-href="PARA Method" href="3-resources/para-method.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">PARA Method</a>
<br><a data-href="Zettelkasten Note Taking" href="2-areas/droplet/zettelkasten-note-taking.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Zettelkasten Note Taking</a>
<br><a data-href="Molecular Zettelkasten" href="2-areas/droplet/molecular-zettelkasten.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Molecular Zettelkasten</a> <br><a data-href="Developing a Note Taking Systems" href="2-areas/clouds/developing-a-note-taking-systems.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Developing a Note Taking Systems</a> Is there anything to back up how people consume and write differently?
]]></description><link>2-areas/clouds/why-note-taking-fails.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2-Areas/Clouds/Why Note Taking Fails.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 02:12:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Emergent Note Taking]]></title><description><![CDATA[In order for notes to develop novel ideas you need to be intentional about what you've learned from something and how it my connect to other ideas. Otherwise you run the risk of being repetitive from the content you consume. Typically ideas come from reading content anyway, but when we fail to capture that we also fail to capture the nuance of our insights.This is where using a Zettelkasten system can provide value. The idea here is to be intentional about rewording insights from other sources to 1. ensure you're paying attention and 2. begin introducing perspective to the content you consume. After creating enough of these atomic notes, you may find you've realized some new connections and from that you can create structured notes. These structured notes aim to be wholly new ideas seeded from inspiration you've consumed.The biggest value I've found it provide is it challenges me to specifically word out and decide what I'm learning or seeing as I connect dots rather than moving backwards from an idea. When you start with an idea, there is no structure or clarity of where that came from or why you believe it should be making new content.
Idea????ContentSourceSourceSourceInsightIf you base your ideas off of moments or sudden "eureka" moments, you risk recreating content you've consumed in the past. The core insights you believe you're providing become muddy. What's your idea and what's someone elses? And then you need to go back and find sources to fill out gaps to make your idea more concrete. This isn't an awful way of doing it, but you're putting the car before the horse and over invest in ideas before they've fully formed.
IdeaSourceSourceInsightContent
Zettelkasten encourages a structured note-taking experience that I find avoids these pitfalls. Ideas don't pop up from no where, their origins become distinct and tangible. By writing notes you consume in your own words, it's clear what's your insight and what is just a rewording of other's content. When you have an idea, you need to intentionally connect the dots or take a leap from an existing note. You don't write reactively, you write proactively. And instead of filling gaps you start with a mostly formed insight as you lead into new content creation.
<a data-href="Molecular Zettelkasten" href="2-areas/droplet/molecular-zettelkasten.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Molecular Zettelkasten</a>
<br><a data-href="Zettelkasten Note Taking" href="2-areas/droplet/zettelkasten-note-taking.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Zettelkasten Note Taking</a> <br><a data-href="Developing a Note Taking Systems" href="2-areas/clouds/developing-a-note-taking-systems.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Developing a Note Taking Systems</a>
<br><a data-href="Why Note Taking Fails" href="2-areas/clouds/why-note-taking-fails.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Why Note Taking Fails</a>
]]></description><link>2-areas/clouds/emergent-note-taking.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2-Areas/Clouds/Emergent Note Taking.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 02:09:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Organizing Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[There are more in depth reasons why PARA may be a good method but this insight is specifically why it works for me and my needs.I use PARA to reduce friction by flattening out folder structures. Navigating folders can be hectic, and content can get buried. Additionally, categorization like that tends to be fluid and changing. Here's an example
WorkVRAMDRAMCPUPersonalGPUNoteTakingAdminToolsBlogWritingNoteTakingToolsLoadTestingDemoPersonalBlogComputingMeetingDNSReadingGPUInsightsI may originally think splitting my folders into Personal and Work make a lot of sense. But as a create new notes, I actually realize it's more useful to me to switch the categories to Computing and Productivity right?
MemoryComputingVRAMDRAMCPUProductivityGPUDNSReadingNoteTakingAdminToolsBlogWritingNoteTakingToolsLoadTestingDemoPersonalBlogComputingMeetingGPUInsights
Well that's also arbitrary. And thinking back to what we mentioned before, I want something that fits my note taking and consuming experience. I don't consume or write notes based on where they exist, I interact with notes based on their purpose. This is why PARA works especially well from this perspective.
VRAMDRAMCPUGPUNoteTakingAdminToolsBlogWritingNoteTakingToolsLoadTestingDemoPersonalBlogComputingMeetingRaw NotesProjectsOn Going Ideas/KnowledgeResources/Source NotesNo Longer UsedGPUInsightsDNSReading
You can see here now my notes or organized more on how I'm thinking about them than what they can be categorized as. This is where an implementation of PARA works well.P -&gt; Projects: If I'm ever looking for projects with end dates in mind that I'm actively working on I can go to this section for that
A -&gt; Areas: If I have an ongoing series of notes that have no end planned those can be together to aggregate insights.
R -&gt; Resources: Full sources/links/resources can live together as a sort of ingestion and aggregation section
A -&gt; Archive: A dumping ground for content that's no longer being actively usedAdditionally I have a Raw notes section I call Inbox for anything that needs to find a home but for now just needs to be written down.This leads to an incredibly streamlined way of creating notes, and we've effectively reduced friction. However in terms of gaining insights or creating new ideas, this still doesn't really encourage that, it leads to lots of notes being taken but not a lot of ideas being generated or connections being made.
<a data-href="PARA Organization" href="2-areas/droplet/para-organization.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">PARA Organization</a> <br><a data-href="Learning and Productivity Frameworks" href=".html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Learning and Productivity Frameworks</a>
<br><a data-href="Emergent Note Taking" href="2-areas/clouds/emergent-note-taking.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Emergent Note Taking</a>
<br><a data-href="Why Note Taking Fails" href="2-areas/clouds/why-note-taking-fails.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Why Note Taking Fails</a>
]]></description><link>2-areas/clouds/organizing-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2-Areas/Clouds/Organizing Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 01:55:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Developing a Note Taking Systems]]></title><description><![CDATA[Note-taking and writing have many frameworks and some are going to work better for other people. A lot of time peers ask me how I take notes, what I suggest, what tools I use, what I automate etc.Unfortunately any answer I provide fails to provide lasting value as it's my note taking system. It works for me. It was emergent from years of trying things, adapting them, and taking portions of certain processes and putting them together.But even more so, it's adaptive to my current interests and focus. When I first started taking many more notes I started using PARA because I wasn't able to find a structure that was clear to me where notes went. When I wanted to create and write I introduced Zettelkasten because I was unable to work backwards from an end result. These tools are more useful within the context of your needs rather than some holy aggregate of the best techniques around.This extends to tooling. Obsidian, bear, evernote, M365, these all can provide value depending on what you need. A comparison on which is the best will never work. A comparison of features will always work.The key insight is this: I recommend continuously learning and experiencing new systems, testing them, and implementing the parts that do work while throwing out the parts that don't. That frankestein you create is the perfect note taking system.My note taking system is formed from a combination of experience and my goals. I want to create technical content, I want to make novel emergent content that isn't restating things without adding something new. I also want to take notes in a way that could be useful to myself in the future, even small insights or thoughts. I don't want to feel restricted by any processes, when I hit motivation to write or learn, I don't want to remember my tagging system or make connections to old notes.Reduce FrictionNo complexsystemsNo expectationof orderlynessNavigableEmergentContentNew writingMy Note TakingSystemIdentifyknowledge gapsGoalsRequirementsOrganizationCreationProcessingSystem
After you know your goals and requirements you can create the following:
<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Organizing Notes" data-href="Organizing Notes" href="2-areas/clouds/organizing-notes.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">An organization system</a>
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Emergent Note Taking" data-href="Emergent Note Taking" href="2-areas/clouds/emergent-note-taking.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">A note creation system</a>
A note processing system
These should all aim to achieve the goals of your note taking
This is how I come across things like Zettelkasten and PARA. Not with the explicit aim to change my note taking system, but consuming it, testing it, and considering new approaches.
<br><a data-href="Zettelkasten Note Taking" href="2-areas/droplet/zettelkasten-note-taking.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Zettelkasten Note Taking</a>
<br><a data-href="PARA Method" href="3-resources/para-method.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">PARA Method</a>
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Molecular Zettelkasten" data-href="Molecular Zettelkasten" href="2-areas/droplet/molecular-zettelkasten.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Digital Zettelkasten</a> <br><a data-href="Why Note Taking Fails" href="2-areas/clouds/why-note-taking-fails.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Why Note Taking Fails</a>
]]></description><link>2-areas/clouds/developing-a-note-taking-systems.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2-Areas/Clouds/Developing a Note Taking Systems.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 01:55:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Condo Ownership]]></title><description><![CDATA[This note is an aggregate experience of what purchasing and owning a condo in NYC is like.
Resources: Council of New York Coops &amp; Condos: <a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://www.cnyc.com/" target="_self">https://www.cnyc.com/</a> List of droplets that contribute to or support this insight Link to related clouds, sources, or potential applications Open questions or unexplored angles
]]></description><link>2-areas/clouds/condo-ownership.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2-Areas/Clouds/Condo Ownership.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 01:52:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[My Note Taking System (WIP)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Type: [Blog post/Video/Newsletter/etc.]
Target Audience: [Specific audience]
Platform: [Where it will be published]
Status: [Draft/Review/Published]
Publication Date: [Target or actual date][Opening that captures attention][Main point you want to convey]
Point 1: Backed by <a data-href="Cloud 1" href=".html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Cloud 1</a>
<br>Point 2: Backed by <a data-href="Cloud 2" href=".html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Cloud 2</a>
<br>Point 3: Backed by <a data-href="Cloud 3" href=".html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Cloud 3</a>
[What you want readers to do]
<br><a data-href="Developing a Note Taking Systems" href="2-areas/clouds/developing-a-note-taking-systems.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Developing a Note Taking Systems</a> <br><a data-href="Why Note Taking Fails" href="2-areas/clouds/why-note-taking-fails.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Why Note Taking Fails</a> <br><a data-href="Emergent Note Taking" href="2-areas/clouds/emergent-note-taking.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Emergent Note Taking</a>
<br><a data-href="Organizing Notes" href="2-areas/clouds/organizing-notes.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Organizing Notes</a> [Actual content ready for publication]
Follow-up content: [Related pieces]
]]></description><link>1-projects/storm/my-note-taking-system-(wip).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">1-Projects/Storm/My Note Taking System (WIP).md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 01:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[my-note-taking-system]]></title><description><![CDATA[MemoryComputingVRAMDRAMCPUProductivityGPUDNSReadingNoteTakingWorkVRAMDRAMCPUPersonalGPUNoteTakingAdminToolsBlogWritingNoteTakingToolsAdminToolsBlogWritingNoteTakingToolsVRAMDRAMCPUGPUNoteTakingAdminToolsBlogWritingNoteTakingToolsLoadTestingDemoLoadTestingDemoLoadTestingDemoPersonalBlogPersonalBlogPersonalBlogComputingMeetingComputingMeetingComputingMeetingRaw NotesProjectsOn Going Ideas/KnowledgeDNSReadingResources/Source NotesNo Longer UsedGPUInsightsGPUInsightsGPUInsightsDNSReadingFolder-style 1Folder-style 2Objective Based Note takingReduce FrictionNo complexsystemsNo expectationof orderlynessNavigableEmergentContentNew writingMy Note TakingSystemIdentifyknowledge gapsGoalsRequirementsOverviewOrganizationCreationProcessingSystemIdea????IdeaSourceSourceInsightContentContentSourceSourceSourceInsightNo Processing - IdeaProcessed Idea]]></description><link>2-areas/__assets/my-note-taking-system.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2-Areas/__assets/my-note-taking-system.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 01:35:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Drawing 2025-10-10 21.13.54]]></title><link>2-areas/__assets/drawing-2025-10-10-21.13.54.excalidraw.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2-Areas/__assets/Drawing 2025-10-10 21.13.54.excalidraw.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 01:13:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[gap-between-notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[RawNotesYouProcessedNotesTagGroupFilterFilter1-4x the effort of the original note takingConsumeNotesYouCreate- Unstructured- Chaotic- Disconnected- RapidYouConsume- Grouped- Tagged- Structured- Well paced- SearchableNotes]]></description><link>2-areas/__assets/gap-between-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2-Areas/__assets/gap-between-notes.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 00:39:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Molecular Zettelkasten]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is Wanderlootes expansion of zettlekasten for a digital note taking system like obsidian. He has the same resource/atomic note, but splits structured notes into "molecules" and "alloys". Where molecules are insights gathered from a group of atoms and an alloy is a targeted or complete work.[ORIGINAL QUOTE FROM SOURCE - below the line]]]></description><link>2-areas/droplet/molecular-zettelkasten.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2-Areas/Droplet/Molecular Zettelkasten.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 14:34:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[PARA Organization]]></title><description><![CDATA[PARA is a useful system for breaking down notes into categories. Specifically it removes the difficulting of focusing on organizing around folders or categories, which does work for some and focuses on a flat folder strategy. Projects are for short-term projects that are have a deadline. Areas is ongoing work or specialities that grow. Resources are sources, sometimes with notes but mostly reference material being aggregated. And Archive is anything no longer being deemed useful.]]></description><link>2-areas/droplet/para-organization.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2-Areas/Droplet/PARA Organization.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 14:32:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zettelkasten Note Taking]]></title><description><![CDATA[Zettelkasten comes from a writer who wanted to allow for emergent and disconnected ideas to easily come from content consumed. It starts with an atomic note or a zettel which is isolated to a single idea reworded from a source. These notes are linked to structured notes or hubs and these are cohesive insights or ideas gained from a combination of notes. It's better for recall and it relates to how the brain naturally thinks about things (in theory).[ORIGINAL QUOTE FROM SOURCE - below the line]]]></description><link>2-areas/droplet/zettelkasten-note-taking.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2-Areas/Droplet/Zettelkasten Note Taking.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 14:32:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Introduction to the Zettelkasten Method]]></title><description><![CDATA[Zettelkasten is a personal, hypertext-style method for thinking and writing built from small, atomic notes (“Zettel”) that each have a unique ID, a short body in your own words, and references. Notes are densely linked (with explicit link context) to form a web of ideas; structure notes act as hubs or tables of contents to navigate big topics. Inspired by Niklas Luhmann’s prolific paper system (with fixed addresses and a register for entry points), modern Zettelkasten favors software-agnostic plain text, timestamps for IDs, and rigorous connectivity over mere collection. It takes practice, but the payoff is organic growth, easier recall, smoother writing, and the ability to tackle complex work by developing insights through connections.]]></description><link>3-resources/introduction-to-the-zettelkasten-method.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3-Resources/Introduction to the Zettelkasten Method.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 14:30:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[PARA Method]]></title><description><![CDATA[
The PARA system—created by Tiago Forte—organizes all digital information into four categories: Projects, Areas, Resources, and Archives. Projects are short-term, actionable goals with clear outcomes; Areas are ongoing responsibilities you maintain over time; Resources are collections of reference materials or topics of interest for potential future use; and Archives store inactive items from any category for later reference. This simple framework replaces complex filing rules with a consistent workflow that can be applied across all tools (like Evernote, Google Drive, or your computer), helping you focus on action instead of re-organizing information.
]]></description><link>3-resources/para-method.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3-Resources/PARA Method.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 14:24:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A Brief History & Ethos of the Digital Garden]]></title><description><![CDATA[
Digital gardening is a philosophy and web publishing style that treats personal websites as living, evolving collections of ideas, rather than fixed, chronological blogs. Instead of polished, time-stamped posts, gardens are contextually linked, imperfect, and continuously tended — a return to the exploratory ethos of the early web. Public thinking, emerging ideas incomplete ideas
]]></description><link>3-resources/a-brief-history-&amp;-ethos-of-the-digital-garden.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3-Resources/A Brief History &amp; Ethos of the Digital Garden.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 14:19:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[House Work]]></title><description><![CDATA[Paint colors
Swiss Coffee: eeece1 -- Base
Passion Vine: 87846b -- Accent
Potters Clay: b98766 -- Primary Color <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://encycolorpedia.com/b98766" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://encycolorpedia.com/b98766" target="_self">Benjamin Moore Potters Clay / 1221 / CC-360 / b98766 Hex Color Code, RGB and Paints</a>
<br>Head over heals: efded2 -- Secondary <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://encycolorpedia.com/efded2" rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://encycolorpedia.com/efded2" target="_self">efded2 Hex Color Code, RGB and Paints</a>
👏 🫂 ❤️ 😬
“test2” is not created yet. Click to create.“Test Drawing” is not created yet. Click to create.Flooring Company:
NYC Floor Pro, 4700 for flooring, 5700 for stain, 2 days of work, 3 days with a stain,217 634 6968 df Duffy Wood Vitalize, 4300 to do refinish, 2 days
Painting Company:
JP - bad reviews high price
Painters plus - good price pretty good reviews
3600 everything included KD Cares
50% up front
50% at the end
Adam Wood Vitalize
Breaker ?
4300 to do refinish
2 days
How thick are the hardwood floors, and do you know the spec
220 electrical box<br>Bed frame: <a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://tatamiroom.com/cgi-local/catalog.pl?category=PLATFORM_BEDS-10#1" target="_self">https://tatamiroom.com/cgi-local/catalog.pl?category=PLATFORM_BEDS-10#1</a><br>
Splurge: <a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://www.thuma.co/products/classic-bed?variant=40242991038569" target="_self">https://www.thuma.co/products/classic-bed?variant=40242991038569</a><br>
<a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Thuma/comments/toqqnj/images_of_tatami_room_frame_thuma_competitor/" target="_self">https://www.reddit.com/r/Thuma/comments/toqqnj/images_of_tatami_room_frame_thuma_competitor/</a> ]]></description><link>1-projects/house-work.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">1-Projects/House Work.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 01:00:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lizzi House Advice]]></title><description><![CDATA[Butcher Block - block off kitchen, trash behind
thin accent chair
stone coffe table
ikea - linen curtains
tulip shades
parachute linen
leaf table you can push back and open up
nordic knots - rugelegant man cave
smoke room
]]></description><link>1-projects/lizzi-house-advice.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">1-Projects/Lizzi House Advice.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 23:39:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[cloud-home-drawing]]></title><link>excalidraw/cloud-home-drawing.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Excalidraw/cloud-home-drawing.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 01:09:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>